

# Ferhat Adıbelli

Nationality: Turkish

(+90) 5459433435

Date of birth: 15 Nov 1991

**Gender:** Male

**☑ Email address:** ferhatadibelli9@gmail.com

**Website:** <a href="https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/">https://ferhatadibelli0.github.io/Portfolio/</a>

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ferhat-adibelli-330b27235/

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/19093788/ferhat-adibelli

• Address: Gazeteci Hasan Tahsin Cad., No:77, Karabağlar, 35150 İzmir (Turkey)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I'm Ferhat. I am from Turkey, I live in Turkey .As a FullStack Developer, I`m very passionate and talented about **Re actJS**, **NextJS**, **NodeJS**, **ExpressJS**, **MongoDB**, **MySQL** . I devoted myself to learn, implement, adapt and create through my life to build smart web apps to help people and improve life quality around the world. As a Web Developer with 14 months of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery, and maintenance.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

#### **Bachelor of Science**

Turkish Military Academy - Ankara [ 2010 - 2014 ]

Field(s) of study: Industrial and Systems Engineering

Final grade: 3.65/4

#### Master's degree

**Gazi Univercity - Ankara** [ 2020 - Current ]

Field(s) of study: Computer Forensic

### **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Very good at programming in: HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Boostrap, Jquery, Javascript / React ecosystem: ReactJS, React Router, Redux, Typescript / Backend: NodeJS, Express, socket.io / RESTful api / Git / Github / graphQL / DenoJs / nextjs / Agile (Scrum) / Postman / FireBase / SQL (MySQL) / Basic knowledge of JIRA / Heroku Cloud

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Frontend Developer**

**Alme Tech** [ Feb 2022 - May 2022 ]

Country: Turkey

Building user interfaces for websites and/or web applications Working with ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript Creating self-contained, reusable, and testable modules and components Writing some end-to-end test on JestJS

#### **Freelancer**

*Upwork* [ Oct 2021 – Jan 2022 ]

Country: Turkey

Upwork helped me find my first job as a Frontend Developer.. It allows me to focus on what is most important for my clients - product and project development.

#### **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

### ReactJS -- The Complete Guide

Academind

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1UPC\_WHLoWUOf9ADO-6JEahHS7nIzeJb0/view?usp=sharing

### **ReactJS -- Web Programming**

**BTK Academy** 

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1GIUX8brBrknCW8iVHf1Wg CLPz g7vMr/view?usp=sharing

### NodeJS -- The Complete Guide

Academind

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1QxMxt8Wh-j9NF83Sqqsbr8I3E6rRcaqK/view?usp=sharing

# Git & Github -- Version Control System

BTK Academy

https://drive.google.com/file/d/17g fC7fDGiHUKurpCb3R6 6AxzE91zq4/view?usp=sharing

## **Language Competency**

American Culture School

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1HOzdEH-8ytlH\_u9XtqXbyaSJIGwNmwDa/view?usp=sharing